zoya.com 2014-06-25

# Art of Beauty Privacey Policy

Go Back

Welcome! 

\- or -

Forgot your password? Click here

Please Choose One: 

Or 

Professional Accounts

**Licensed salon & spa professionals can set up a Professional Account which entitles them to professional only pricing, professional only promotions and additional educational and marketing resources available to our salon & spa customers.**

If you already have a Professional Account with us, please sign in below with your email and password in the **"Sign In to My Professional Account"** section.

To create a Salon - Spa Professional Account, please enter your email and a valid Cosmetology License in the section called **"Create a Professional Account"** below and click the **"Create Account" button.** You will then be asked for additional information.

Sign In to Your Professional Account 

Create a Professional Account 

Welcome! 

Please Choose One: 

Or 

**What our Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers any personal information that Art of Beauty obtains from you when you use services on our site. This policy does not cover the practices of companies that Art of Beauty does not own or control, or the actions of people that Art of Beauty does not employ or manage.

Our Privacy Policy may change in the future. Please check back periodically to see if we have made any changes. By using this site, you agree to the terms of our Legal Statement and our Terms and Conditions of Sales. **

What Personal Information is Collected

**

We may ask you to share personal information with us. Whether you choose to give Art of Beauty information is completely up to you, but keep in mind that if you withhold information, you may not be able to use some of our services.When Personal Information is Collected Art of Beauty will ask you for information, including some personal information, if you use one of several services: **

Becoming a Registered User

**

In order to register, you need to share some personal information, such as your name and e-mail address. You do not have to be a registered user to visit Art of Beauty's web pages. But, you will have to register if you want to place orders or make full use of our services. **

Making a Purchase

**

When you buy something on Artofbeauty.com (this includes www.zoya.com, www.qtica.com, www.qticasmartspa.com), you have to supply a billing address, phone number, shipping address, and credit card information. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of Art of Beauty. You can choose to store information needed to make a purchase, such as your shipping and billing addresses in the My Account - Profile page. If you change your mind about storing this information, you can amend or delete it by going to the relevant area of the My Account-Profile page and following the instructions. You can access this section using your registration password.

**Our Ratings & Reviews Question & Answer Service**

When you use the Ratings & Reviews or the Question & Answer services you will need to become a registered user (if you aren’t already one) and any personal information you submit will become part of your profile, as maintained by Art of Beauty.

**How Art of Beauty Protects Your Information**

We realize that our customers trust us to protect their personal information and we take that task seriously. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.

We use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") authentication to guarantee the confidentiality of online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the Internet help protect your online transaction information from third party interception.

We never display your full credit card number once it has been entered. We will only reveal the last four digits of your credit card for verification purposes. We urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone or share your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.

Unfortunately, despite all of our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all Internet use. As a result, we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk. **

How Art of Beauty Uses Your Personal Information

**

Art of Beauty collects personal information primarily to make our services more rewarding for you to use. We usually use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences. We may also use your information to contact you for account and promotional purposes. We do not sell or share your personal information. In the event that another company buys the assets or stock of Art of Beauty, your personal information may then belong to another entity. **

How to Avoid Receiving Art of Beauty Materials by Email

**

We use e-mail addresses to send out announcements with information about Art of Beauty new products, Special Promotions and updates. If you receive an e-mail and want to avoid further messages, look at the end of the e-mail for instructions on how to remove yourself from the mailing list.

**Who Views Your Personal Information**

Art of Beauty may share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mails, analyzing customer data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, investigating fraudulent activity, conducting customer surveys, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not disclose your personally identifiable information for other purposes.

We currently share aggregate information about our customers with advertisers and marketing partners. This information does not identify individual users.

Any personal information that you include in your profile or any content submitted when using the Ratings & Reviews or the Question & Answer services will be displayed on Art of Beauty web sites, so please consider before submitting any such content.

Personal information may be disclosed if required by law. Art of Beauty does not currently sell or license personal information. **

Art of Beauty's Use of Web Beacons

**

We have included web beacons on some of our web pages. Art of Beauty uses web beacons to transfer data (such as purchase and site usage history). Art of Beauty may provide this data to companies that assist Art of Beauty in data research and analysis; these companies are prohibited from using this data for any other purpose. The analysis and research helps Art of Beauty to determine customer preferences and improve Art of Beauty's offerings. Art of Beauty may also rely upon third parties to assist with the use and implementation of the web beacons.

Definition of web beacon: A web beacon, sometimes called a pixel, is a graphic image or small string of code, that is included on web pages or in an email to enable the transfer of data. Web beacons can be used by companies for several purposes such as reporting web site traffic, customer preferences, advertising effectiveness, and general auditing. **

Questions About This Policy

**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the content or practices of our website, you can contact Art of Beauty directly at:

Art of Beauty Inc  
Legal Department  
PO Box 22349  
Cleveland OH 44122
